Adult Education Audio and Video Collection
Adult Education Audio and Video Collection
- Reel to reel tapes
  - 0473-01/21 People Under Communism. National Association of Educational Broadcasters. (Box 8)
    - 0473-18 ‘National Self-Determination: Soviet Style’ by Professor Philip E. Mosely of Columbia. (Box 8)
    - 0473-19 "The Strange Behavior of the Soviet Diplomats" by Professor Philip E. Mosely of Columbia. (Box 8)
    - 0473-20 ‘The Strange Behavior of the Soviet Diplomats" by Professor Philip E. Mosely of Columbia. (Box 8)
    - 0473-21 Through the Iron Curtain. Documentary by the BBC. (Box 8)
  - 0479-01/10 The Power to Govern. (Box 9)
    - 0479-01 The Control of Power: The origin and background of Separation of Powers. (21:12) (Box 9)
    - 0479-02 Government by Judges: The Judiciary Role as Interpreter of the Constitution. (27:05) (Box 9)
    - 0479-03 Executive Leadership: The Office of President of the United States. (14:15) (Box 9)
    - 0479-04 Scope of Legislative Powers: The Constitutional Role of Congress. (14:00) (Box 9)
    - 0479-05 Interaction between President and Congress on Domestic Policy: Cooperation of Stalemate. (16:00) (Box 9)
    - 0479-06 Interaction between President and Congress on Foreign Policy: Can the President go it Alone? (15:00) (Box 9)
    - 0479-07 Separation of Powers and Administrative Agencies: Governmental Restraint vs. Efficiency. (Box 9)
    - 0479-08 The Impact of Separation of Power on Liberty: Does it Protect Individual Rights? (18:00) (Box 9)
    - 0479-09 Alternatives to Separation of Powers: Is There a Better System of Government? (22:00) (Box 9)
    - 0479-10 Separation of Powers Today: An Evaluation. (17:25) (Box 9)
  - 0480-01/14 The Ways of Mankind. (Box 9)
  - 0481-01/15 The Ways of Mankind. Series II. (Box 10)
  - 0482-01/17 Test City Coordinators Meeting. Chicago, June 9-14, 1952 (Box 10)
  - 0483-01/09 Man is Not a Thing. (Box 10)
    - 0483-01 Freud in Perspective. (Box 10)
    - 0483-02 Freud and the American Child. (Box 10)
    - 0483-03 Freud and the American Mother. (Box 10)
    - 0483-04 Freud and the American Father. (Box 10)
    - 0483-05 Freud, Authority and the American Conscience. (Box 10)
    - 0483-06 Freud and the American Democracy. (Box 10)
    - 0483-07 Freud and the American Consumer. (Box 10)
    - 0483-08 Freud and Religion. (Box 10)
    - 0483-09 Freud and the Social Sciences. (Box 10)
  - 0484-01/02 The Community of Ideas. (Box 10)
  - 0485-01/02 The Mysterious Universe. (Box 10)
  - 0486-01/02 The World Beyond the Atom. (Box 10)
  - 0487-01/02 Specia1ization. (Box 10)
  - 0488-01/02 The Six Philosophic Systems of India. (Box 10)
  - 0489-01 Political Forces in France. (Box 10)
  - 0490-01/08 Pre-Galaxy Conference on Adult Education. Racine, Wisconsin., 1969 (Box 11)
  - 0491-01 Fleming, Arthur. Keynote address. (Galaxy Conference on Adult Education) (Box 11)
  - 0492-01 United States Secretary of State Rogers. Address on Mideast Affairs. (Galaxy Con­ference on Adult Education) (Box 11)
  - 0493-01/10 Ways of Mankind. Ways to Justice. (Box 11)
  - 0494-01/02 ERIC/AE National Advisory Board Meeting, June 4-6, 1968 (Box 11)
  - 0495-01/03 ERIC/AE National Advisory Board Meeting, December 3-4, 1968 (Box 11)
  - 0496-01/03 ERIC/AE National Advisory Board Meeting, April 17-18, 1969 (Box 11)
  - 0497-01/02 ERIC/AE National Advisory Board Meeting, October 23-24, 1969 (Box 11)
  - 0498-01 Jeffersonian Heritage. (Box 11)
  - 0499-01/02 What is the Place of TV in Education? Audio recording of telecast over WGBH-TV, Boston, Mass., May 2, 1957 (Box 11)
  - 0500-01/15 Arden House Conference on Continuing Education and Education for Public Responsibility, March 27-31, 1960 (Box 12)
  - 0501-01/06 Randall, Clarence. A Business Man Looks at the Liberal Arts. (Audio Recording from WGBH-FM, Boston, Mass.) A series of 3 lectures sponsored by the Fund for Adult Education Lecture and Harvard University, 1956 (Box 12)
  - 0502-01/08 Bryson, Lyman. Teaching Ourselves to be Free. A series of 3 lectures sponsored by the Fund for Adult Education and University of Wisconsin, September 28, 30; October 1, 1953 (Box 12)
  - 0503-01/03 Fleming, A. S. The Liberal Arts and the Government of Men. A series of 3 lectures sponsored by the Fund for Adult Education, February 25-27, 1958 (Box 12)
  - 0504-01/05 Fund for Adult Education/Leadership Training Summer Institute, Rancho Santa Fe, California, June 21-29, 1955 (Box 12)
  - 0504-06/11 Fund for Adult Education/Leadership Training Summer Institute (cont.), Rancho Santa Fe, California, June 21-29, 1955 (Box 13)
  - 0505-01/03 Tape I-Brogan, Dennis. Political Warfare. A Lecture given at the Institute of World Affairs, December 16, 1952. Tape 1, 2, 3-Katz, Milton. European Economy and the Russian-American conflict. A Lecture given at the Institute of World Affairs (Box 13)
  - 0506-01/05 Watts, Orville. Economic Education. (Includes discussion with citizen's group in Los Angeles, California), May 29, 1952 (Box 13)
  - 0507-01/05 Way Beyond the West. (Box 13)
  - 0508-01/04 The Ideal City. (Box 13)
  - 0509-01/11 The People Talk Back. (Box 13)
  - 0510-01/03 AEA Conference on Organization of Health Service. (Box 13)
  - 0511-01/05 Oral History Project
    - 0511-01 Hamilton Stilwell (Box 14)
    - 0511-02 Lloyd Schram (Box 14)
    - 0511-03 Thurman White (Box 14)
    - 0511-04 Olive McKay (Box 14)
    - 0511-05 John Holden (Box 14)
  - 0531-01/03 Human Freedoms. A series of group discussions. (Box 14)
  - 0532-01 Savicivich, D. Adult Education in Yugoslavia. Exeter conference on Comparative Adult Education, June 19-25, 1966 (Box 14)
  - 0533-01 National Council on the Aging. Technology and the Aging: A Report of the 13th Annual Meeting. (Box 14)
  - 0534-01/05 Syracuse University. Publications in Adult Education Conference, Minnowbrook. Proceedings., June 8-10, 1971 (Box 14)
  - 0535-01 Eight ventures into Thought. Hutchins, Robert. Is Democracy Possible? (Eight Ventures into Thought: A discussion series prepared by the Department of Adult Programs of the Unitarian Universalist Association.) (Box 14)
  - 0536-01/06 The Years Between: A Series on Youth and Family Living. (Box 15)
  - 0537-01 Adler, Mortimer. Is Government Necessary? (The Great Ideas: a program devoted to understanding the ideas by which we live.) Recorded from KGO-TV, December 6, 1953 (Box 15)
  - 0538-01 Adler, Mortimer. The Nature of Government. (The Great Ideas: a program devoted to understanding the ideas by which we live.), recorded from KGO-TV., December 13, 1953 (Box 15)
  - 0539-01 Adler, Mortimer. The Ideal of Human Government. (The Great Ideas: a program devoted to understanding the ideas by which we live.), recorded from KGO-TV, December 27, 1953 (Box 15)
  - 0541-01/05 Conference on the Continuing Education Unit, Virginia Tech,. Proceedings., April 27-28, 1972 (Box 15)
  - 0542-01 Tyler, Ralph. Discussions of evaluation and evaluation systems in Adult Education. [Tape 1 of 3], adulted_028 (Box 15)
  - 0542-02 Tyler, Ralph. Discussions of evaluation and evaluation systems in Adult Education. [Tape 2 of 3], adulted_029 (Box 15)
  - 0542-03 Tyler, Ralph. Discussions of evaluation and evaluation systems in Adult Education. [Tape 3 of 3], adulted_030 (Box 15)
  - 0543-01 Charters, Alexander. What is the Unique Responsibility of the University for Continuing Education? Given at Michigan State University Seminar on Leadership in University Adult Education, February 5, 1962; adulted_031 (Box 15)
  - 0544-01 What Should be the Role of the Federal Government in Providing Medical Care? The Citizens of the U.S.A. Debate Topic sponsored by National University Extension Association Committee on Discussion and Debate. Speakers: Carl Mann and Edmund Muskie., 1963 (Box 15)
  - 0546-01 Houle, Cyril O. Discussion of Adult Education in Europe., adulted_023 (Box 15)
  - 0547-01 Moore, Willis. Contributions of Classic Greece to Democratic Thought. (American Ideals, 2). Shaneres, Hartley. The Fight Against Communism. (Window in the World, 2). (Box 16)
  - 0548-01 Years of Crisis. CBS News Special. Edward R. Murrow, moderator., 1953 (Box 16)
  - 0549-01 Walker, Turnley. World of Paperback Books. (See for Yourself) (Box 16)
  - 0550-01 The Eccentric. (American Adventure) (Box 16)
  - 0551-01 This I Believe. (Radio program). Paul G. Hoffman, speaker, February 20, 1953 (Box 16)
  - 0617-01 The Surplus Man. (Box 16)
  - 0618-01 A look at U.S. press from Abroad. (Box 16)
  - 0619-01 Crisis of Identity in a Workless World. (Box 16)
  - 0751-01/11 National Adult Education Conference, Nov 16-20, 1972 (Box 16)
  - Unidentified, assorted reel-to-reel tapes; some labeled, some not; various sizes and toipcs; 37 tapes (Box 20)
- Audiocassettes
  - 6884-01 Conversations from Wingspread - Religious Activity in America Today. (Box 17)
  - 6885-01 Is Bigger Really Better - Corporate Growth. (Box 17)
  - 6886-01 India-an interview by Dan Price, speakers were John P. Lewis and Philip Talbot. (Box 17)
  - 6887-01 Brazil - The Indigenous People. (Box 17)
  - 6888-01 The Foreign Student Experience in the U.S. (side 1); Culture Shock and the Foreign Student (side 2). (Box 17)
  - 6889-01 South Africa, Human Rights, and the United Nations. (Box 17)
  - 6890-01 The Tragedy of Ulster - Tragedy of Northern Ireland. (Box 17)
  - 6891-01 International and Comparative Education. Dr. Vincent Tinto., 11/16/76 (Box 17)
  - 6892-01 Adult Education – Interview. Speakers: Dr. Charters, CDE Newton Proffitt, in Guyana., adulted_024 (Box 17)
  - 6893-01 Adult Education: Trends, Issues, and Problems. J. Crowley., adulted_002 (Box 17)
  - 6894-01 History of Non-Commercial Broadcasting. R.J. Blakely., 7/31/75 (Box 17)
  - 6895-01 Adult Education-Trends and Issues., adulted_001 (Box 17)
  - 6896-01 State and Federal Programs Entitlement. Dr. Norman Kurland. (Box 17)
  - 6897-01 Public Televisions and College Education-A National Perspective. Douglas Bodwell., 3/26/79 (Box 17)
  - 6898-01 Adult Education: Forms They Take (side 1); Who Speaks for the Aging. David Hobman. (side 2)., 7/27/76; 4/5/77; adulted_003 (Box 17)
  - 6899-01 Thursday Morning Roundtable. WCNY-FM, University College. Dr. Tolley's Address., 11/17/77 (Box 17)
  - 6900-01 The Role of Humanities in Continuing Education., 10/30/79 (Box 17)
  - 6900-02 Perspectives on Adult Education. (BAD TAPE), 10/30/79; adulted_004 (Box 17)
  - 6901-01 Community Education, speaker Donald Tobias., 10/24/79 (Box 17)
  - 6902-01 Continuing Education in Great Britain. Colvin Bourn., 9/25/79 (Box 17)
  - 6903-01 Continuing Education: The New Partnerships., 9/12/79 (Box 17)
  - 6907-01 Course in Adult Education and Broadcasting by Robert Blakely., Summer 1979 (Box 17)
  - 6907-02 BLANK TAPE. (Box 17)
  - 6907-03/04 Course in Adult Education and Broadcasting, by Robert Blakely., Summer 1979 (Box 17)
  - 6908-01/02 Satellite Communications Demonstration, by Dr. Gus Root., 4/25/75 (Box 17)
  - 6909-01 Interview - Mr. Bruce Davis, interviewer Walter Varner, 7/74 (Box 17)
  - 6910-01 Interview - Bruce Davis, interviewer Walter Varner (voices very faint and muffled). Summer 74. (Box 17)
  - 6911-01/02 WCNY-Tour and Discussion (sides 1-4)., 3/19/75 (Box 17)
  - 6912-01/06 Interviews (Box 17)
    - 6912-01 Interview, Mr. N. Nacarella (side 1); Anna Byre, Urban League (side 2), 4/18/75 (Box 17)
    - 6912-02 Interview - Mr. David Rowe. (Box 17)
    - 6912-03 Interview - Mr. Arthur Stock (side 1); Mr. Tony Fisher (side 2)., 5/22/1975 (Box 17)
    - 6912-04 Interview. Mr. Arthur Stock. (Box 17)
    - 6912-05 Interview - Kwesi Ampene, in Ghana (side 1); Ms. Nancy Klein, (side 2)., 5/26/1975 (Box 17)
    - 6912-06 Interview - Dr. John Cotman (side 1); Roger Lord (side 2)., 6/2/75 and 6/3/75 (Box 17)
  - 6913-01/18 Ron Hilton interviews (Box 17)
    - 6913-01 Interview - Ron Hilton (interviewer) and Mr. Walter Varner (interviewee) (side 1); Ron Hilton (interviewer) and Dr. Lee Porter (interviewee) (side 2)., 10/28/74 and 10/30/74 (Box 17)
    - 6913-02 Interview - Ron Hilton (interviewer) and Mr. G. Sullivan (interviewee) (side 1); Ron Hilton (interviewer) and Dr. J. Wright (interviewee) (side 2)., 11/4/74 and 11/5/74 (Box 17)
    - 6913-03 Interview. Ron Hilton (interviewer) and Dr. Abram Friedman (interviewee), 11/6/74 (Box 17)
    - 6913-04 Interview. Ron Hilton (interviewer) and Dr. Hilton Power (interviewee), 11/6/74 (Box 17)
    - 6913-05 Interview. Ron Hilton (interviewer) and Dr. Anita Martin (interviewee) (side 1); Ron Hilton (interviewer) and Ms. Patricia Bohn (side 2)., 11/6/1974 (Box 17)
    - 6913-06 Interview. Ron Hilton (interviewer) and Dr. Paul Kazmierski (interviewee) (side 1); Ron Hilton (interviewer) and Dean Robert Koch (interviewee) (side 2)., 3/12/1975 (Box 17)
    - 6913-07 Interview. Ron Hilton (interviewer) and Dean Robert Koch (interviewee), 3/12/75 (Box 17)
    - 6913-08 Interview. Ron Hilton (interviewer) and Mr. Bernard Logan (interviewee), 3/14/75 (Box 17)
    - 6913-09 Interview. Ron Hilton (interviewer) and Ms. Betty Ward (interviewee), 3/21/75 (Box 17)
    - 6913-10 Interview. Ron Hilton (interviewer) and Father Norbert Henry (interviewee}, 4/1/75 (Box 17)
    - 6913-11 Interview. Ron Hilton (interviewer) and Joseph Gray (interviewee), 4/15/75 (Box 17)
    - 6913-12 Interview. Ron Hilton (interviewer) and Mr. C. Hoskins (interviewee), 4/18/75 (Box 17)
    - 6913-13 Interview. Ron Hilton (interviewer) and Mr. Francis Macy (interviewee), 4/28/75 (Box 17)
    - 6913-14 Interview. Ron Hilton (interviewer) and Mr. Francis Macy (interviewee), 4/28/75 (Box 17)
    - 6913-15 Interview. Ron Hilton (interviewer) and Agnes Drummond (interviewee) (side 1); Mr. Neil Carr (interviewee) (side 2)., 5/12/75 and 5/13/75 (Box 17)
    - 6913-16 Interview. Ron Hilton (interviewer) and Mrs. Elise Wiehl (interviewee) (side 1); Mr. Arnold Naroff (interviewee) (side 2)., 5/13/1975 (Box 17)
    - 6913-17 Interview. Ron Hilton (interviewer) and Mrs. Wilona Peace (interviewee) (side 1); Ms. Doris Moss (interviewee) (side 2)., 5/13/1975 (Box 17)
    - 6913-18 Interview. Ron Hilton (interviewer) and Mr. Joseph Winfrey (interviewee), 5/13/75 (Box 17)
  - 6923-01/02 Competency Based Adult Education, Mr. Joseph Bosco, 3/5/80 (Box 17)
  - 6924-01 Research in Adult Education, Dr. Roger Boshier, 3/5/80; adulted_005 (Box 17)
  - 6925-01 Seminar in Adult Education, Dr. J. R. Kidd [Tape 1 of 3], 3/19/80; adulted_011 (Box 17)
  - 6925-02 Seminar in Adult Education, Dr. J. R. Kidd [Tape 1 of 3], 3/19/80; adulted_012 (Box 17)
  - 6925-03 Seminar in Adult Education, Dr. J. R. Kidd [Tape 1 of 3], 3/19/80; adulted_013 (Box 17)
  - 6926-01 Adult Education in Response to Political and Social Issues. Malcolm Knowles [Tape 1 of 2], 2/2/80; adulted_007 (Box 17)
  - 6926-02 Adult Education in Response to Political and Social Issues. Malcolm Knowles [Tape 1 of 2], 2/2/80; adulted_008 (Box 17)
  - 6927-01/02 Adult and Continuing Education, Malcolm Knowles. The Metropolitan Committee on Adult and Continuing Education. (Box 17)
  - 6928-01/04 Survey Class: Dr. Charters. (Tape 6928-01 is damaged.), 4 tapes (Box 17)
  - 6929-02/03 Objectives, Evaluation, Etc. Dr. Charters. (Box 17)
  - 6930-01 Methodology - Philosophy of Methods., adulted_006 (Box 17)
  - 6931-01 Learning Theory and Classroom Practice in Adult Education., adulted_av_027 (Box 17)
  - 6932-01 Adult Education - Caribbean Conference, Georgetown, Guyana. (Box 17)
  - 6933-01 Frontier College. (Box 17)
  - 6934-01 Interview on Dr. Edwin Townsend Coles. (Box 17)
  - 6935-01 Problems Facing Adult Education., adulted_009 (Box 17)
  - 6936-01 The Tougher Side of Immigration, Toronto, Canada. (Box 17)
  - 6937-01 The Fourth Estate (student journalists' critiques of University lectures). (Box 17)
  - 6938-01 The Role of the University in Adult Education, from the campus of U.B.C., adulted_010 (Box 17)
  - 6939-01 Community Development in Sicily. (Box 17)
  - 6940-01 Fairbank House Lives Again - The History of Fairbank House. (Box 17)
  - 6941-01 Canadian Citizenship Procedures. (Box 17)
  - 6942-01 Writing Poetry, by Robertson Davis. (Box 17)
  - 6943-01 Radioactive Fallout and the 200th Anniversary of Battle of the Plains of Abraham, speaking are Dr. Kenneth McNeil and Marcell Ferribol, respectively, CBS Radio-Trans Canada Network. (Box 17)
  - 6944-01 Caribbean Citizens. (Box 17)
  - 6945-01 Address to an American Labour Service - Conference., adulted_025 (Box 17)
  - 6946-01 A Philosophy for Adult Educators. (Box 17)
  - 6947-01 Life Before Death in the Corporate State. (Box 17)
  - 6948-01 Teaching in Different Countries. (Box 17)
  - 6949-01 Continuous Learning Interview - Self Education Process and the Bank of Montreal Monthly Letter., adulted_026 (Box 17)
  - 6950-01 Canadian Nationalism-Canadian/American Relations. (Box 17)
  - 6951-01 Alberta Days and Nights. (Box 17)
  - 6952-01 Interview with Dr. Tyrone Guthrie. (Box 17)
  - 6953-01 Biography of Ned Corbett. (Box 17)
  - 6954-01 Concern - Tension Between Natural Resources and Human Resources in Canada's North. (Box 17)
  - 6955-01 The University and Economic Changes in the Canadian Economy. (Box 17)
  - 6956-01 University of the West Indies 25th Anniversary, conference - University Forum/Radio Education Unit of the University of the West Indies. (Box 17)
  - 6957-01/02 Documentary Film, by Art Chetwynd. (Box 17)
  - 6958-01 Fircroft College by Harry Neetin and Open University by Lady Lee. (Box 17)
  - 6958-02 Adult Education in India. (Box 17)
  - 6959-01 African Socialism as the Goal of the Tanzania Nation. (Box 17)
  - 6959-02 Questions and Answers, The High Commissioner from Tanzania. (Box 17)
  - 6960-01 Interview. Adult Education Tanzania, speaker Father McBunda. (Box 17)
  - 6961-01 Adult Education Seminar, Dr. Rosalind Loring. [Tape 1 of 2], 3/29/80; adulted_014 (Box 17)
  - 6961-02 Adult Education Seminar, Dr. Rosalind Loring. [Tape 2of 2], 3/29/80; adulted_015 (Box 17)
  - 6962-01 Adult and Continuing Education Metropolitan Committee, Dr. Loring., 3/29/80 (Box 17)
  - 6963-01/03 Resources for Educators of Adults/Show and Tell, Mr. Ray Ast., 11/14/79 (Box 17)
  - 6964-01/04 The Need for Information Resources, Conference ­ Clearinghouse of Resources for Educators of Adults., 11/15/1979 (Box 17)
  - 6965-01 Tape is marked incorrectly. (Box 17)
  - 6966-01/02 Continuing Adult Education, Conference - Coalition of Adult Education Organizations., 2/21/80 (Box 17)
  - 6967-01/42 Interviews by Joseph Jacques. (Box 17)
    - 6967-01 Interview by Joseph Jacques. Dr. Mary Armstrong (interviewee), 3/19/72 (Box 17)
    - 6967-02 Interview by Joseph Jacques. Mary Louise Collins (interviewee)., 5/8/72 (Box 17)
    - 6967-03 Interview by Joseph Jacques. Adult Education, Robert J. Blakely., 4/22/72 (Box 17)
    - 6967-04 Interview by Joseph Jacques. Concept of Education, Robert J. Blakely., 4/11/71 (Box 17)
    - 6967-05 Interview by Joseph Jacques. Adult Education, Dr. Ld P. Bradford., 4/15/72 (Box 17)
    - 6967-05 Interview by Joseph Jacques. Adult Education, Dr. Ld P. Bradford., 4/15/72 (Box 17)
    - 6967-07 Interview by Joseph Jacques. Dr. Paul L. Essert (interviewee)., 3/22/72 (Box 17)
    - 6967-08 Interview by Joseph Jacques. Dr. Paul L. Essert (interviewee)., 3/22/72 (Box 17)
    - 6967-09 Interview by Joseph Jacques. W. C. Hallenbeck (interviewee)., 4/24/72 (Box 17)
    - 6967-10 Interview by Joseph Jacques. W. C. Hallenbeck (interviewee)., 4/24/72 (Box 17)
    - 6967-11/15 Interview by Joseph Jacques. W. C. Hallenbeck (interviewee)., 4/24.,.25, 26, 27, 1972 (Box 17)
    - 6967-16 Interview by Joseph Jacques. Dr. Sam Hand (interviewee)., 5/30/72 (Box 17)
    - 6967-18 Interview by Joseph Jacques. Dr. Eugene I. Johnson (interviewee)., 5/17/72 (Box 17)
    - 6967-19/26 Interview by Joseph Jacques. Andrew Hendrickson (interviewee). (Box 17)
    - 6967-27/34 Interview by Joseph Jacques. Dr. McClosky (interviewee)., 4/10, 11, 12, 13, 14, 1972 (Box 17)
    - 6967-35/41 Interview by Joseph Jacques. Dr. Ralph Beckett Spence (interviewee)., 5/15/72 (Box 17)
    - 6967-42 Interview by Joseph Jacques. Robert J. Blakely (interviewee). (Box 17)
  - 6969-01 Adult Education Seminar, Dr. John Ohliger. [Tape 1 of 2], 2/13/80; adulted_016 (Box 17)
  - 6969-02 Adult Education Seminar, Dr. John Ohliger. [Tape 2of 2], 2/13/80; adulted_017 (Box 17)
  - 6970-01/02 Adult and Continuing Education, Dr. John Ohliger and Dr. Graham Leonard., 2/14/80 (Box 17)
  - 6971-01 Adult Education Seminar, Dr. Clifford Winters., adulted_018 (Box 17)
  - 6972-01 Selection and Training of Community Development Workers. (Box 17)
  - 6973-01 Interview: Extension Work in Adult Education, Father George Topshee. (Box 17)
  - 6974-01 Ontario Indians. (Box 17)
  - 6975-01 Adult Education in India. (Box 17)
  - 6976-01 The Involvement of Universities. (Box 17)
  - 6977-01 Continuous Learning - Cliff McIntosh. (Box 17)
  - 6978-01 Fundraising and Work with the YMCA in Montreal. (Box 17)
  - 6979-01 Continuous Learning - Adult Education Principally at the University of B.C. (Box 17)
  - 6980-01 The Counseling Services of George Brown College. (Box 17)
  - 6981-01 Continuous Learning - Canadian Voice of Women. (Box 17)
  - 6982-01 Continuous Learning - Experiences at Sir George Williams University. (Box 17)
  - 6983-01/02 Literacy Training and the Ideas of Paolo Freire. (Box 17)
  - 6984-01 Adult Education-Counseling Needs of Adults. (Box 17)
  - 6985-01 Education - Breakthrough into Tomorrow. (Box 17)
  - 6986-01 Interview - Experiences in Special Education. Speaker is Dr. Sam Laycock. (Box 17)
  - 6987-01 Interview - The Thomas Moore Institute. Speaker is Father E. O'Connor. (Box 17)
  - 6988-01 Theatre and Drama in the West Indies - Caribbean. (Box 17)
  - 6989-01 Homer Watson and the Doon School of Fine Art. (Box 17)
  - 6990-01 Liberal Adult Education and the Development of Community Leadership. (Box 17)
  - 6991-01 Prescription for Living Through Recreation. (Box 18)
  - 6992-01 Interview - Canadian Theatre, speaker is Robertson Davis. (Box 18)
  - 6993-01 The Legalization of Marijuana. (Box 18)
  - 6994-01 Inner Science Workshop and the Educational Theory of Dr. Charles Kelly based on Wilhelm Reich. (Box 18)
  - 6995-01 Interview - Continuous Learning: Experiences with the University of B.C. Extension Department, speaker is Gordon Selman. (Box 18)
  - 6996-01 The Man with the Magic Lantern, a tribute to educator Ned Corbett. (Box 18)
  - 6997-01 Interview with Monsignor Frank Smyth. (Box 18)
  - 6998-01 National Library Week, Toronto, Canada. (Box 18)
  - 6999-01 Which Way Out? Environmental Crisis - Case Against Standard Oil. The militant labor forum. (Box 18)
  - 8011-01 Questions directed to Professor Marcuse. (Box 18)
  - 8011-02 Power and Powerlessness - White Radicals. (Box 18)
  - 8019-01 Working Session on Adult Education - International Aid and Poverty, The International Council for Adult Education., June 2 and 3, 1980 (Box 18)
  - 8050-01 The Formal School System. (Box 18)
  - 8051-01 Education in Japan. (Box 18)
  - 8052-01 BLANK TAPE. (Box 18)
  - 8053-01 Cable T.V. and Adult Education. (Box 18)
  - 8054-01 Hartford ABC House. (Box 18)
  - 8055-01 Education in India. (Box 18)
  - 8056-01 Tutor Training in Great Britain. (Box 18)
  - 8057-01 Adults as Learners. (Box 18)
  - 8074-01 Adult Education and Its Role in Public Policy. Dr. Charters' Tapes. (Box 18)
  - 8075-01 I.Q. and Its Relationship to Adult Education. Dr. Charters' Tapes. (Box 18)
  - 8076-01 Critical Issues in Adult Education: An International Perspective. Intercouncil on Adult Education Organization. Dr. Charters' Tapes. (Box 18)
  - 8167-01/03 Humanizing Adult Education Research. Ronald Hilton, Ph.D. Interviews Howard McClusky, 11-8-79 (Box 18)
  - 8168-01/02 Humanizing Adult Education Research. Ronald Hilton, Ph.D. Interviews Dr. Paul Sheats, Jack London, Portland, Oregon, 10/28/78 (Box 18)